{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "The new student _____ by the teacher .",
      "correctAnswer": "is helped",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is help"
    },
    {
      "question": "The dog _____ by Ben .",
      "correctAnswer": "is walked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "Biscuits _____ here .",
      "correctAnswer": "are made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is make"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cat _____ by Ben .",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't walked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "isn't walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sandwiches _____ here .",
      "correctAnswer": "aren't made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "aren't make"
    },
    {
      "question": "Baseball _____ with nine players on the team .",
      "correctAnswer": "is played",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is play"
    },
    {
      "question": "The problem _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is solved",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is solve"
    },
    {
      "question": "The heavy boxes _____ by Moby .",
      "correctAnswer": "are carried",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is carry"
    },
    {
      "question": "The pizza _____ by Max .",
      "correctAnswer": "is made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is make"
    },
    {
      "question": "The sandwich _____ in two pieces .",
      "correctAnswer": "is cut",
      "incorrectAnswers": "cuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "Apples _____ in the bowl .",
      "correctAnswer": "are put",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is put"
    },
    {
      "question": "The houses _____ very fast .",
      "correctAnswer": "are built",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is build"
    },
    {
      "question": "The food _____ by my mom .",
      "correctAnswer": "is bought",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is buys"
    },
    {
      "question": "The criminals _____ by the police .",
      "correctAnswer": "are caught",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is catch"
    },
    {
      "question": "My bike _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is stolen",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is steal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dinner _____ by my mother .",
      "correctAnswer": "is cooked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "The floors _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are washed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is wash"
    },
    {
      "question": "The bread _____ with a knife .",
      "correctAnswer": "is cut",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is cuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "The company _____ by him .",
      "correctAnswer": "is run",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is runs"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ presents .",
      "correctAnswer": "am given",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am give"
    },
    {
      "question": "Presents _____ to me .",
      "correctAnswer": "are given",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is give"
    },
    {
      "question": "The doctor _____ for .",
      "correctAnswer": "is sent",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is send"
    },
    {
      "question": "The film _____ about .",
      "correctAnswer": "is talked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "The rule _____ to the students .",
      "correctAnswer": "is explained",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is explain"
    },
    {
      "question": "These oranges _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are peeled",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are peel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Vegetables _____ here .",
      "correctAnswer": "are sold",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is sell"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is never _____ of .",
      "correctAnswer": "taken care",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is take care"
    },
    {
      "question": "The children _____ after .",
      "correctAnswer": "are looked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is look"
    },
    {
      "question": "The boy _____ to school .",
      "correctAnswer": "is taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is take"
    },
    {
      "question": "Football _____ all over the world .",
      "correctAnswer": "is played",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is play"
    },
    {
      "question": "The letter _____ by pen .",
      "correctAnswer": "is written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is write"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ to school .",
      "correctAnswer": "is not taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is not take"
    },
    {
      "question": "London _____ by many people each year .",
      "correctAnswer": "is visited",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wild animals _____ to attack humans .",
      "correctAnswer": "are known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is know"
    },
    {
      "question": "English classes _____ here every day .",
      "correctAnswer": "are taught",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are teach"
    },
    {
      "question": "The bread _____ every morning .",
      "correctAnswer": "is baked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is bake"
    },
    {
      "question": "Paper _____ from wood .",
      "correctAnswer": "is made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is make"
    },
    {
      "question": "These rooms _____ every day .",
      "correctAnswer": "are cleaned",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "This picture _____ by Kate .",
      "correctAnswer": "is painted",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "The flowers _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are watered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are water"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "The new student _____ # by the teacher .",
      "correctAnswer": "is helped",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is help"
    },
    {
      "question": "The dog _____ # by Ben .",
      "correctAnswer": "is walked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "Biscuits _____ # here .",
      "correctAnswer": "are made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is make"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cat _____ # by Ben .",
      "correctAnswer": "isn't walked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "isn't walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sandwiches _____ # here .",
      "correctAnswer": "aren't made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "aren't make"
    },
    {
      "question": "Baseball _____ # with nine players on the team .",
      "correctAnswer": "is played",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is play"
    },
    {
      "question": "The problem _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is solved",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is solve"
    },
    {
      "question": "The heavy boxes _____ # by Moby .",
      "correctAnswer": "are carried",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is carry"
    },
    {
      "question": "The pizza _____ # by Max .",
      "correctAnswer": "is made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is make"
    },
    {
      "question": "The sandwich _____ # in two pieces .",
      "correctAnswer": "is cut",
      "incorrectAnswers": "cuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "Apples _____ # in the bowl .",
      "correctAnswer": "are put",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is put"
    },
    {
      "question": "The houses _____ # very fast .",
      "correctAnswer": "are built",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is build"
    },
    {
      "question": "The food _____ # by my mom .",
      "correctAnswer": "is bought",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is buys"
    },
    {
      "question": "The criminals _____ # by the police .",
      "correctAnswer": "are caught",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is catch"
    },
    {
      "question": "My bike _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is stolen",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is steal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dinner _____ # by my mother .",
      "correctAnswer": "is cooked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "The floors _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are washed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is wash"
    },
    {
      "question": "The bread _____ # with a knife .",
      "correctAnswer": "is cut",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is cuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "The company _____ # by him .",
      "correctAnswer": "is run",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is runs"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # presents .",
      "correctAnswer": "am given",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am give"
    },
    {
      "question": "Presents _____ # to me .",
      "correctAnswer": "are given",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is give"
    },
    {
      "question": "The doctor _____ # for .",
      "correctAnswer": "is sent",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is send"
    },
    {
      "question": "The film _____ # about .",
      "correctAnswer": "is talked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "The rule _____ # to the students .",
      "correctAnswer": "is explained",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is explain"
    },
    {
      "question": "These oranges _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are peeled",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are peel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Vegetables _____ # here .",
      "correctAnswer": "are sold",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is sell"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is never _____ # of .",
      "correctAnswer": "taken care",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is take care"
    },
    {
      "question": "The children _____ # after .",
      "correctAnswer": "are looked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is look"
    },
    {
      "question": "The boy _____ # to school .",
      "correctAnswer": "is taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is take"
    },
    {
      "question": "Football _____ # all over the world .",
      "correctAnswer": "is played",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is play"
    },
    {
      "question": "The letter _____ # by pen .",
      "correctAnswer": "is written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is write"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ # to school .",
      "correctAnswer": "is not taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is not take"
    },
    {
      "question": "London _____ # by many people each year .",
      "correctAnswer": "is visited",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wild animals _____ # to attack humans .",
      "correctAnswer": "are known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is know"
    },
    {
      "question": "English classes _____ # here every day .",
      "correctAnswer": "are taught",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are teach"
    },
    {
      "question": "The bread _____ # every morning .",
      "correctAnswer": "is baked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is bake"
    },
    {
      "question": "Paper _____ # from wood .",
      "correctAnswer": "is made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is make"
    },
    {
      "question": "These rooms _____ # every day .",
      "correctAnswer": "are cleaned",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "This picture _____ # by Kate .",
      "correctAnswer": "is painted",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "The flowers _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are watered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are water"
    }
  ]
}